KRISTIN JACOBSEN

CONTACT

1373 Holland Hill, Southlake, TX 76092 kristinjacobsenn@gmail.com 817 907 4849

EDUCATION

COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY
Certification in Coding & Web
Development
In Progress, expected Jan 2021

TEXAS CHRISTIAN UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Science Fashion Merchandising, 2014 Minor: English & Writing

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator HTML/CSS JQuery/Javascript

EXTRA

Recently relocated to Dallas area from New York City due to COVID-19.

Dual citizenship with Luxembourg, EU

Conversational in French

Hobbies: sailing, tennis, painting, cooking

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Public relations, marketing, and social media professional with experience in creative solutions, media communication, client relations, key relationship building, event planning, trend analysis, graphic design, web development, copy and creative writing, editing, planning, analytics, and project management.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SENIOR ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE
Purple Public Relations (New York City)
February 2019 - present // furloughed due to COVID-19

- Develop and maintain key editor and influencer relationships.
- Secure top media placements for travel and hospitality clients: EDITION
 Hotels (London, Barcelona, Abu Dhabi, Bodrum, Shanghai, Sanya), The
 Norman Tel Aviv, and Chapter Roma (Rome), by creative pitching, press
 trips, and strategic partnerships.
- Assist with various hospitality and lifestyle projects ranging from social media consulting to planning and executing launch events and openings. Projects include: Rockefeller Center, SuperReal at Cipriani, and Omar's La Boîte dining club.

ACCOUNT MANAGER
ACCOUNT COORDINATOR
INTERN
Celine Kaplan Public Relations (New York City)
June 2014 - Jan 2019

- Began as Intern and worked up to Manager within four years
- Maintained key media and influencer relationships.
- Designed press releases and wrote pitches for clients: Ladurée US, ERES (Chanel Group), Maison Francis Kurkdjian (LVMH), Christophe Robin, Darphin (Estee Lauder) and additional projects.
- Assisted in the creation and execution of PR strategies.
- Organized and oversaw client events and product presentations.
- Managed office; hiring and managing coordinators and interns, maintaining calendar, sample trafficking, shipments, and expenses.

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER Ladurée US (New York City) Feb 2016 - June 2019

- Managed the social media strategy and community for Ladurée US (@ladureeus)social media accounts.
- Created, planned, developed, edited, and curated content using various social planning tools (Sprout, Sales Force, etc...)
- Created monthly analytical reports.
- · Facilitated and oversaw all influencer partnerships.
- Tripled Instagram following within 3 years.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

STYLIST | Lilly Pulitzer (New York City) June 2014 - Feb 2015

PR INTERN | Starworks Group (New York City) Summer 2013

SALES INTERN | Free People (Chicago, IL) Summer 2012

PR INTERN | Live Loyal PR (Los Angeles, CA) Summer 2011